Thomas Wiltshire

Hello, my name is Thomas. I'm a hard-working, passionate games programmer that is currently living in Ballarat, Victoria. Over the last 3 years, I have been studying at the Academy of Interactive Entertainment (AIE) to obtain a Bachelor of Games and Virtual Worlds (Programming).

Fraser Street Mount Pleasant, VIC 3350

+64 466661042 thomas.wiltshire14@icloud.com thomaswiltshire.com

EXPERIENCE

Advance Computing, Kyabram, Victoria — Software Developer Trainee

January 2016 - December 2016 (1 Year)

I worked at Advance Computing for around a year where I started a Certificate 3 in Information Technology as a part of my traineeship in software development. I learnt a lot during my time at Advance, had many amazing experiences, obtained a greater knowledge of business and got my first real taste of the software development industry.

McDonald's Australia, Echuca, Victoria— Kitchen Crew Member

March 2015 - January 2016 (1 Year)

I worked at McDonald's Echuca within the kitchen environment, being trained in most aspects. During my time here, I gained irreplaceable skills and experience in teamwork, punctuality, leadership and of course, cleaning and cooking.

Kyabram Community and Learning Centre, Kyabram, Victoria — IT Technicians Assistant (Work Placement)

March 2014 (½ Year)

As a part of my VCAL studies, we were required to find work placement positions for at least one day a week. I worked at KCLC in the IT department helping with various repair jobs, network issues and general computer assistance.

EDUCATION

Academy of Interactive Entertainment (AIE), Melbourne, Victoria — Bachelor of Games and Virtual Worlds

January 2017 - December 2019

Kyabram P-12 College/Kyabram St Augustine's College, Kyabram, Victoria — Primary School / High School

January 2002 - December 2014

TOP SKILLS

Software Development.

C# / C++ Programmer.

Knowledge in both PC and Macintosh systems.

Friendly, Approachable and can communicate with people of all ages.

Punctual, Polite and Enthusiastic.

Team Working Skills and Experience.

Troubleshooting.

NOTABLE PROJECTS (FOUND AT THOMASWILTSHIRE.COM)

Zombie Game - Video Game.

Toy Wars - Video Game.

Gypsy's Tale - Video Game.

Technical Design Document - Gypsy's Tale.

REFERENCES

Mark Schumann - Advance Computing. **Ph: 0358523122**

Kyle Taylor - Past Team Member. **Ph**:

Jono Withall - Past Colleague. **Ph**: